Tell me, tell me, tell me your problems I'm here for you Just try, just try, just try to stay sober It's eating you And they say you are a monster, but what I see's a child Your eyes, your eyes are glowing red And your tongue has caught on fire
So let go, let go of your fire Let it go, let go of your fire Live it up 'til we crash and there's smoke in the air Let it go, let go of your fire
You play, you play, you play up to them But they're not around Don't be, don't be so rough with me When you are a gem
And they ask how I can love you, when all they see is this But I see the things that you can't contain and what it does to you
So let go, let go of your fire Let it go, let go of your fire Live it up 'til we crash and there's smoke in the air Let it go, let go of your fire
Let go, let go of your fire Let it go, let go of your fire Live it up 'til we crash and there's smoke in the air Let it go, let go of your fire
So let go, let go of your fire Let it go, let go of your fire Live it up 'til we crash and there's smoke in the air Let it go, let go of your fire
Let go, let go of your fire Let it go, let go of your fire Live it up 'til we crash and there's smoke in the air Let it go, let go of your fire
